Think Like a Man Too is a comedy, romance film directed by Tim Story.
All the couples are back for a wedding in Las Vegas, but plans for a romantic weekend go awry when their various
misadventures get them into some compromising situations that threaten to derail the big event.
Isaac, played by Adam Brody.
Dominic, played by Michael Ealy.
Jeremy Kern, played by Jerry Ferrara.
Mya, played by Meagan Good.
Candace Hall, played by Regina Hall.
Cedric Ward, played by Kevin Hart.
Think Like a Man Too is a 2014 American romantic
comedy film directed by Tim Story.
It is the sequel to the 2012 film Think Like a Man, based on Steve
Harvey's 2009 book Act Like a Lady, Think Like a Man.
The script was written by David A.
Newman and Keith Merryman, with Will Packer returning as producer
but now under his Will Packer Productions banner.
The film stars Michael Ealy, Meagan Good, Regina Hall, Terrence J, Taraji P.
Henson, Romany Malco, Gabrielle Union, Jerry Ferrara, Wendi McLendon-Covey, Gary Owen and
Kevin Hart, with Jennifer Lewis and La La Anthony in supporting roles.
Think Like a Man Too was released on June 20, 2014, by Screen Gems.
It grossed $70.2 million against a $24 million budget.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
relationship problems, sequel, las vegas, misadventure.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.